Where a grandparent can have a grandchild
call them and say, hey, I made a mistake
and I've run into somebody and I need some
money. And then an attorney gets on and
says, we're actually going to need you to
send us over here. It's a $10 billion
industry a year in fraud, which is in
addition to what we saw earlier, which
that happened 10 years ago. It's like
what's happened since this Cindy's son had
actually taken her life. These are some of
the things that actually can can do it in
real time. And so when a grandparent
actually imagine a future where a
grandparent doesn't need to use username
and passwords. They just grab their phone,
push on an apps, log in, and they can
actually see all of their assets, all of
their ability to pay things, all of the
things that they own, all the contacts.
And it's actually managed by someone
that's given guardianship rights from an
organization like a state to be able to
help manage that grandparent. Maybe it's
accounts. Maybe it's paying bills. Maybe
it's paying different vendors. Maybe it's
different assets and how to pass them from
one generation to another. Maybe it's
currencies. Maybe it's the ability to
actually manage context, not just for your
child, but also for grandparents. There's
a lot of confusion when people get into
that environment. And then the ability to
actually take these types of things and
actually drop from one environment to
another to actually make it easy for them
to pay. So if you wanted to pay a utility
bill or you wanted to pay a grandchild,
it's all integrated and simple. So that's
a good example of a grandparent type
guardianship reality with a simple app
that you can pull down, log in today and
actually start using these types of
things. It also works with children. So
the ability for children to be able to be
managed from what apps are they using to
what sites are they going to. There's a
lot of functionality and opportunities
there. So I just want to say thank you for
those specifically Sam Smith, Phil
Windley. These are people that have
dedicated their lives to solving this
problem. Tim, I mean, this is real. This
is a nucleus here in Utah that we can
actually make a real difference. But
ultimately, it's actually all of you that
have said, this is a problem that I want
to learn about and a problem that I want
to be able to be a part of the solution in
the future. So thank you for coming and
thank you for actually understanding
what's happening here in Utah. But it's
really the world. It's a problem that
society has, a responsibility in our
generation. Like when all of us were born,
we didn't have the cell phones. We didn't
have the internet. And when we pass on,
we've got to pass on a better legacy than
what's currently there. So thank you for
Chris and all the hard work that he does
to put this together and those at the
state that truly are aligning with this
effort. Because I know it's not easy to
put these parts and pieces together. When
we went and searched the world, we could
not find a body like this. We went to the
government in the DC. We went here. We
went in. It's just amazing to see the
heart, the alignment to support someone
like Cindy who 10 years ago lost a son.
That's real. In this university. That
young man went to this university 10 years
ago. And here we are. So thank you for
being here and understanding some of these
concepts.